findmyshift.com 2012-12-26

# Privacy policy » Findmyshift

## What data does Findmyshift store?

As a general rule we try to keep personal information about you and your business to a minimum, only storing what is necessary for the system to function. This is why most data fields in the system are optional.

When signing up as a manager for your free trial we ask for your email address, your first name, a password and a name for your schedule. You are have the option to enter email addresses and mobile telephone numbers for staff so you can communicate directly with them via the website, however these contact details are not required.

Apart from storing all data entered by managers and staff, Findmyshift also stores email support logs, access logs and trace logs of any errors that may occur. This helps us ensure the site is operating as expected. Detailed access logs which include the IP address of the user may be kept for up to a week before being removed. Payment information such as credit card details are all processed by a third party payment provider (PayPal) so no credit card details are ever handled or stored by Findmyshift. It is possible that PayPal may store certain credit card details for future purchases and it is worth noting that their privacy policy may differ from ours.

## What does Findmyshift do with your information?

Findmyshift only ever uses your data for populating your schedule and any associated reports. We don’t share, sell or export your data to any third party that is not directly involved in the delivery of this service. Findmyshift will never use personal data for marketing or business development and will only contact you if necessary for administrative or operational purposes associated with your subscription.

Unless troubleshooting a problem with your service, Findmyshift staff will only ever access your data when authorised by you to do so.

## How does Findmyshift safeguard your data?

Ensuring that your data is secure is very important and we take this responsibility seriously. As a result, all sensitive data you enter is encrypted, including your password, your name and your contact details. All the data associated with your account and your schedules is stored on our servers in a highly secured, world class data centre, protected by a number of layers of physical security.

Furthermore, every 24 hours all customer data is backed up, encrypted and archived to two secure off-site locations.

Findmyshift is also registered with the UK Information Commissioner’s Office (Reg. No. Z3140758) and is fully compliant with the UK’s Data Protection Act, which is in line with most international information protection laws and regulations.

## Can I delete my data?

If you signed up for the free one month trial and haven’t signed up as a customer, your schedule and all data entered will be deleted from our servers after 90 days of inactivity, so no action is required from you. If you’re an existing customer and are thinking of leaving us, please get in touch to discuss any concerns you might have about leaving your data within Findmyshift.

## Does Findmyshift use cookies? If so, how?

Yes, and like most websites, cookies are integral to its operation. In particular, cookies are used to remember your log-in details and to keep your session active whilst using the site. In addition, cookies are also used to remember certain computer and user specific settings. Findmyshift also uses Google Analytics which needs to store a number of cookies to operate correctly.

If you want to know more about how and why cookies are used on websites, please visit [this Wikipedia entry](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie) or get in touch with the team.

## What if I navigate to another website via Findmyshift?

Findmyshift may at times contain links to other websites which are outside of our control and are not covered by our privacy policy. If you access other sites using these links, the operators of these sites may collect and use your information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.

## Where can I find out more information?

If you have a specific question about how we protect your data then please get in touch.
